{
    "id": "3ab2b6b2f8624e379cc4775053a38af2",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ………………………… a deep pit.",
            "description": "Dig is an irregular verb. Its past form is dug.",
            "answers": [
                "dug",
                "dugged",
                "digged"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1275209109c94040a63c7ae8a2072ed4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has always been …………………………. towards animals.",
            "description": "Drawn is the past participle form of draw. ",
            "answers": [
                "drawed",
                "drew",
                "drawn"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ef46c70f8234bc2b923304be7b25588"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t drive if you are …………………………….",
            "description": "Drunk is the past participle form of drink. ",
            "answers": [
                "drank",
                "drunk",
                "drinked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d5a0843a80f049fe98004bf217678ac8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were …………………………….. by the rain.",
            "description": "Driven is the past participle form of drive. ",
            "answers": [
                "driven",
                "drove",
                "drived"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f712c10ea03b44089200c4f82eb442d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. the cats before I went out.",
            "description": "Fed is the past simple form of feed. ",
            "answers": [
                "feeded",
                "fed",
                "fead"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0abd01793d44d5bae416d88d1653b88"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………… above hills and valleys.",
            "description": "Flew is the past simple form of fly.",
            "answers": [
                "flied",
                "flew",
                "flowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39f373f09fce4ff89e0ed78148b71ab2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………….. suspicious.",
            "description": "Grew is the past simple form of grow. ",
            "answers": [
                "growed",
                "grew",
                "grown"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d7e5a9a6c014699a5271533e82afaa2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………………. the painting on the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hanged",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d0866095fc6471c9ee3fabd36f11653"
        },
        {
            "question": "The treasure lay …………………………… for centuries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hid",
                "hidden",
                "hided"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74f34a9c0436452c93617bd5c7d1667b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was badly ……………………………..",
            "description": "Hurt is the past simple and past participle form of hurt. ",
            "answers": [
                "hurt",
                "hurted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fe7e9d15890d4cdf8689e70ade34a1f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. the mirror against the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leant",
                "leaned",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "99befe204c5747bd9bbe2fc3461323b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………………….. the lamp.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lit",
                "lighted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ef7451da9774edc8b883420d5e7c142"
        }
    ]
}